Danny Baldeon Abril

Junior Tech Consultant

As a Junior Tech Consultant, I had the opportunity to work with various clients, giving me valuable experience and expertise working in the tech business. From gaining the role as a Product Analyst at AutomatePro, in which I have collaborated with product owners and the development team to provide personalised and effective solutions that meet their business needs and objectives, to working as an IT floorwalker for iTrain Legal by aiding and providing extra support for first-time users migrating to a new file management system.

Furthermore, the opportunities as a Junior Tech Consultant have allowed me to expand and improve my software development skills, by undergoing a boot camp specialising in front-end and back-end Web Development, for example, to strengthen my Javascript skills, using libraries and frameworks to create and develop applications. Currently, I am studying for my OCP SE11 Java Certification.

Profile		Specialising	Skills	
Phone	07460941234	Front-end Development, Automated Testing,	■ HTML ■ CSS	SeleniumCucumber
Email	dbalabr.work@gmail.com	Behaviour Driven Development, Manual	JavaScriptReact.is	■ Github■ AdobeDocs -
Website	https://salsabaga.github.io/dba_portfolio/	Testing, Wireframing		Markdown Files

Employment

Junior Tech Consultant

Ten10 Solutions, Leeds

Training in Ten10 has given me a strong foundation in project management by understanding the intricacies of Agile methodologies. Moreover, I gained invaluable expertise in Quality assurance, understanding the importance of testing via the principles of testing a product before shipping to production, the application of a test design when planning out a timeline of software testing, and the numerous amount of testing methodologies that I have gained the knowledge of, but also the capability to be accustomed to any method in future projects.

Product Analyst at AutomatePro

September 2022 - December 2022

- At a low-code testing company, my responsibilities at AutomatePro were working with stakeholders, developers, and testers to define product requirements, prioritise features, and ensure alignment with business goals.
- Part of a team writing documentation on all the features and walkthroughs of the product utilising AdobeDoc, breaking down and monitoring each component using JIRA.
- With a focus on improved accessibility of complex technical information of low-code automation workflows by simplifying language and formatting, facilitating effective communication with clients unfamiliar with technical concepts.

IT Floorwalker for iTrain Legal

February 2023 - March 2023

Aid in the gradual integration of clients to a new file storage management system. Primary roles were to guide users in using the new system for document editing, reading, permission enabling, and navigation and integration of the software as a Microsoft extension. In addition, I was to report all bugs, issues, and UI issues to the product manager for future reference when analysing common complaints and creating new ideas and updates for the software.

English Tutor

Tomodachi Factory, Japan

- I provide clear and concise communication skills in teaching English to Japanese speakers, improving their English language proficiency and increasing their confidence when speaking and listening.
- I enable an energized classroom environment and facilitate engaging lessons to maximise student participation.
- My contribution to the company has met with overwhelmingly positive feedback from local elementary and middle schools for
 delivering dynamic and engaging English language lessons that inspired students to deepen their understanding of the language.
 As a result, the program gained a reputation for excellence and attracted the attention of schools in other prefectures, such as
 Saga, who have expressed interest in adopting the curriculum.

Education

Coventry University - 2:1 BA. (Honors) Politics with Year Abroad

September 2016 - June 2020

- Robust theoretical and conceptual approach towards Political and International affairs by utilising and understanding key concepts & theories efficiently and accurately through real-world and historical events.
- Applying, using, and analysing data, such as social, political, and environmental, to find key factors and correlations that shape historical world events, denote decision-making on political choices and policies that shape our society, and understand political forecasts, predictions, climate, and results by realizing the background, historical context, and methodologies used to portray a story.
- Proficient in Microsoft Applications such as Word, PowerPoint, OneNote, and Excel.
- Versatile communication through different languages, undertaking opportunities by learning new languages, and expanding
 my confidence and ability to communicate with people globally. The most notable modules in which I have gained this
 experience has been the "Absolute beginner Japanese" course, understanding correct pronunciation, phrases, and grammar
 to use when I undertook my year abroad in Japan.

STEM Academy/Tech City Academy, London

September 2014 - June 2016

B in A Level Mathematics
B in A Level Further Mathematics
D in A Level Physics